<blog>
	<post>
		<date>December 1, 2022</date>
		<author>Rohit</author>
		<title>New snickerdoodle cookies recipe..</title>
		<summary>
			<image_path>https://images-gmi-pmc.edge-generalmills.com/087d17eb-500e-4b26-abd1-4f9ffa96a2c6.jpg</image_path>
			<text>I'm kicking off cookie season with a new snickerdoodle recipe! It yields snickerdoodles just the way I like them. 
		These classic cookies are crisp around the edges and soft and chewy in the middle.</text>
		</summary>
		<body>I'm kicking off cookie season with a new snickerdoodle recipe! It yields snickerdoodles just the way I like them. 
		These classic cookies are crisp around the edges and soft and chewy in the middle.
		 They're lightly sweet and warmly spiced with cinnamon, and they have a subtle tangy flavor that I find completely irresistible.
        Taste aside, I also love this snickerdoodle recipe because it's so simple to make.
        You can mix up the dough, bake the cookies, and have them ready to eat in under 30 minutes, 
        no chilling required! It's a great recipe to make throughout the holiday season (who would say no to a snickerdoodle on a festive cookie plate?!), 
        but it's also one of our favorites year-round. I hope you love it as much as we do
		</body>
	</post>
	<post>
		<date>December 2, 2022</date>
		<author>Rohit</author>
		<title>Easy Dinner Ideas for Taco Night</title>
		<summary>
			<image_path>https://www.thecookierookie.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/12/oven-baked-spicy-chicken-tacos-6-of-14-650x650.jpg</image_path>
			<text>It doesn't matter if it's Tuesday, Friday, Thursday, or Monday. 
			Any night can be taco night, especially if you keep a stash of tortillas in your freezer!</text>
		</summary>
		<body>
		Do you ever have nights when you just don't know what to make for dinner? When you run through a mental list of easy dinner ideas, but nothing sounds good? 
		If you do, you're in the right place. Below, you'll find 60 healthy dinner recipes that are perfect for busy weeknights. 
		Each one is quick and easy to make, but it still packs a punch of flavor.
        Think roasted veggie tacos with a creamy, zesty sauce. Imagine luxurious baked feta and a comforting pasta ready in under 30 minutes.
        You'll find all that and more among the easy dinner ideas below. I hope you enjoy looking through them! And the next time 
        you're craving something healthy, delicious, and quick, and I hope you try one. Fingers crossed it makes it into your regular rotation. 🙂
		</body>
	</post>
	<post>
		<date>December 3, 2022</date>
		<author>Rohit</author>
		<title>Garlic Bread recipe.</title>
		<summary>
			<image_path>https://www.simplyrecipes.com/thmb/yW9NXC97hUwj5_sGRa8gcle0LSM=/1500x0/filters:no_upscale():max_bytes(150000):strip_icc()/__opt__aboutcom__coeus__resources__content_migration__simply_recipes__uploads__2006__09__Garlic-Bread-LEAD-1-8b9944bb8e7a4fc49094da4d34f7ba50.jpg</image_path>
			<text>In theory, this homemade garlic bread is the perfect side dish. It's quick and easy to make, it goes well with a variety of main dishes,
	 and it also happens to be delicious. So what's the problem?</text>
		</summary>
		<body>
	In theory, this homemade garlic bread is the perfect side dish. It's quick and easy to make, it goes well with a variety of main dishes,
	 and it also happens to be delicious. So what's the problem?
     Well, whenever I make this garlic bread recipe, it doesn't really end up being a side.
	  Of course, Jack and I can't help but sample a few pieces straight from the baking sheet. 
	  By the time it reaches the table, we've already put a pretty good dent in it. And by the end of the meal, 
	  we've nearly polished off the whole batch. So…side dish? For us, I'm not so sure.

	  All that's really to say that we adore this homemade garlic bread, and if you try it, I think you will too. 
	  It's crisp around the edges, soft and buttery in the middle, and saturated with rich, savory garlic flavor.
	   Call it a snack, a side dish, or even half your dinner (oops!). No matter what, it'll be a hit.
		</body>
	</post>
</blog>